wholebodyresearch.com 2017-06-22

# Whole Body Research Privacy Policy

#### Overview

Whole Body Research, LLC (hereafter, "Whole Body Research®," "our," "we," "us") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our members. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that children (i.e. anyone who is under the age of 18) are protected from adult materials. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Whole Body Research®, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit www.WholeBodyResearch.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct the information.

#### Information about You

Upon registration for membership, Whole Body Research® will specifically ask for information about you. We will ask for your full name, billing address, telephone number and credit card number in order to ship you your products and provide you with all of Whole Body Research®'s services.

We use your telephone number only if there is an order-related issue, though because we understand your need for anonymity we will make all attempts to contact you via email. We do not use your telephone number for marketing purposes.

We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for our service. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to not respond.

#### Tracking Information:

Whole Body Research® will collect and store only the following nonpersonally-identifying information from you: the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to our site. We also track your order and billing history so you can access your Whole Body Research® orders and immediately determine which program you've purchased and how you paid for them. This information is password-protected. No one has access to it but you.

As you browse the Whole Body Research® website, cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to track the items you select as you shop, and help us match your address and credit card information with your order so you don't need to retype the information each time you visit our site. Cookies also allow us to gather information to provide you with the best service. It tells us the number and frequency of visitors to our site and its various pages. Third parties may serve some of these cookies. We analyze this data to determine which parts of our site customers like and which parts need improvement. Automatically logged information is also used to analyze trends and to administer the site.

#### Disclosure

We value your security concerns and appreciate the importance of your trust. We strive to maintain reasonable safeguards to protect your personal Information against loss, unauthorized use and or disclosure or personal information, and when transferring information when processing your order.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

Our website's payment gateway is hosted by 1ShoppingCart.com. 1ShoppingCart.com has access to aggregate data about our customers in order to assist 1ShoppingCart.com in analyzing Site performance and making improvements to 1ShoppingCart.com products.

In addition, all orders are processed through Network Merchants, LLC. The personally identifiable information Network Merchants, LLC acquires in processing payment transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which merchants or financial institutions are using their payment services. It may include, for example, the amount of the transaction, the consumer's name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address, and shipping address.

Network Merchants, LLC uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the payment gateway services. Personal information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose.

Network Merchants, LLC stores transaction information on secure computers located in a locked data center. Only a small number of employees involved in the management of the data center have physical access to these computers. Where possible, Network Merchants, LLC encrypts information stored on their computers as a further measure of protection. Network Merchants, LLC uses state-of-the-art firewalls and other security technology to prevent their computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons.

We may share your transaction processing information is VeriSign, which subsequently may share that information to a third party licensor of the fraud prevention scoring services (the "Fraud Service Bureau") solely for use in developing its fraud prevention modeling and for performing the Fraud Services. All your transaction processing information provided to the Fraud Service Bureau shall be subject to written agreement between VeriSign and the Fraud Service Bureau restricting disclosure of any Customer Data to other third parties except as necessary to perform the Fraud Services.

#### California Residents

Many browsers have a "Do Not Track" feature that allows you to instruct websites that you do not want them to track your online activities. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to this feature.

California residents who have provided their personal information to us may request data regarding disclosures of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be submitted to us by email at support@wholebodyresearch.com or at the following mailing address: Whole Body Research, LLC, Attn: Customer Care, 9361 Canoga Ave., Chatsworth, CA 91311. 

Please specify in your communication that you are making a "California Shine the Light" inquiry. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

#### Children's Privacy

We do not specifically market to children under the age of thirteen (13). Children may not use our services, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who address our website. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

#### Security and Access

Whole Body Research® uses a secure socket layer (SSL), which encrypts all information that is transmitted or received. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy for Whole Body Research®, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

#### Contact

If you have any questions concerning our privacy policy you can contact us at support@WholeBodyResearch.com

#### Effective Date

04/25/2017
